Because now I am a little old.   Let
me tell you the truth.  I've recently
turned 30,
and by recently, I mean five years ago
[cheering voice] people here who have
n't turned 30 yet make some noise, quite a lot
of you.  Quite a lot of you.
And people who are above the age of 30 don't don't don't don't make any
noise.  Don't make any noise.  He will get breathless, there
is no use.  Yes no
[appreciation]
Kuch chhuwa baithoge rehne do aa haath people above the
age of 30 give me a heavy bit of tiredness
that's more like it.  That's my jam.  But I am
sure you would relate.  I am sure that
as soon as you celebrate your 30th birthday.  As soon as
iOS 30 is installed.   The
body has just given up.  Every day a
new part of the body hurts.  [laughter]
Daily I had pain here the day before yesterday.  Here,
this head and this lower back keep
hurting.  [laughter]
Woke up that morning with no back pain at all.
I am removing the sheet and searching for the spine.
[laughter]
How did you become spineless?  Without
going to Bollywood.  So many things
[cheering voice] horrible.
People ask me brother where do you live in Gurgaon
?  I live in pain.
[laughter] So many things have changed in life.
Ever since I've turned 30.  Digestion for
example, I remember during college days, whatever you
ate would get digested.  [laughs]
How many stones have we digested?  The doctor is saying that you have a
stone in your kidney.  I said
look carefully, it will be in the stomach.  [laughs]
I have eaten pav bhaji from such and such places during my college days.
This is a pav bhaji shop
next to which [laughs] a flat tyre is being fixed
and next to this is a Sulabh toilet
water tank.   The
same water is flowing, heating the feet,
inhaling smoke, and waking up in the morning.  Nothing is
happening.  Nothing is happening
[cheering voice].
[Praise]
In today's date, look at the flour.
[laughs]
My own [ __ ] gets offended.
[Applause]
Going.  Now I will come again after two days.
Lakshya is not looking well this time.   It
is a fact.  [cheering] It's a fact.
Half the things are not digestible.
Something is happening with the remaining half.  [laughter]
Someone's getting gassy.  Some have
diarrhea, some have constipation, some have
all of the above.  [laughter]
So what's left to eat?  Bottle gourd  They are pushing the gourds.  The
community that used to drink a quarter of whiskey neat,
today asks for celery water after half a point of beer.
[Applause] Four friends meet after four years.  I am
sitting to drink alcohol after drinking one and a half litres of water.
[laughs]
I'm talking to doctors more than friends
today.  [laughter] And I have all the
doctors on speed dial right now.
You name it, have it.  Gastro Astro
all
yes yes and Astro 100% Astro because
when nothing is going well in life
[laughs]
then a person blames Vaastu
that maybe the toilet will be in the North East only
[encouraging voice]
every doctor has given me something or the other to eat on an empty stomach at this time.
[laughter] Someone is
saying antacids on an empty stomach, someone is saying
apple cider on an empty stomach, someone is saying
papaya on an empty stomach, someone is saying soaked almonds on an empty stomach.
Now I have so much stuff to eat on an empty stomach
[laughter]
that breakfast time is not on an empty stomach at all [laughter].   I have
n't been able to have breakfast for two and a half years.
What did you do for breakfast?  Celery Funki I
really liked this Funku.  [laughs] The
way we dress has changed a lot.  I remember going to
buy jeans during college time.
So he is saying Bhaiya, tight fit jeans,
slim fit, absolutely cigarette fish, carrot fish,
absolutely no
air can come in or go out [laughter]
laminate the legs,
make it absolutely vacuum [encouraging voice]
[praise]
wearing jeans, wearing slacks, the difference cannot be seen
[laughter]
wearing jeans in the morning, knees get torn by the evening,
now when I am going to buy jeans, he is saying
Bhaiya,
show me a pajama which fits the pants
[laughter] no no, not the one with a
belt, I
want the one with a drawstring, the buckle of that belt pokes into the big belly.
Now in the meantime the marriage has also taken place.  I also said I got married when I was
30.  So
two life altering events happened to me at the same
time.  So it's been four-five years since
we got married and before that
we dated for four-five years.  So we've been
together for a really, really long time.  Now
we have been together for so long that it has become an
unspoken rule between us.
That the less we both talk to each other, the
better it is for the mental health of both of us.
Because my head hurts whenever she speaks.
[laughs]
And my existence itself is
problematic.
[cheering]
[applause]
You're clapping.  I got scolded for breathing heavily.
[laughter] Will that
suck up all the oxygen?  But no, it is
not that love has ended.  It's love.
Still love but touch wood love.  Yes,
250 people are sitting there to cast an evil eye, brother.  No,
but it's love.  But that you know both of us are
on the same age.  I am 35 she is 34.  So
both of us get very tired after doing very little work.
[laughs] So that's why
every night before we go to sleep, we
massage each other.
We would not have slept less after getting rid of our tiredness.  She turns her back there.  She
steps here.  I massage his feet.
I turn my back here.  I
step there.  She massages my feet.  This
Is Our 69 [laughter]
[applause]
because the actual one is missing out.
[laughter] I'm getting
tired.  I am very nervous.  I can't
[laughs]
But it wasn't always like that.  Like I was genuinely very
passionate about
intercourse as a concept.  Or intercourse was
my jam.
[laughs] I remember at the
age of 19, in the
third year of engineering college, I got my
first girlfriend in my life and at that time,
in the prime of my youth [laughs]
my thoughts used to be like when I get
married, I will have sex every day
[laughs] I used to
leave my office clothes outside every day, such an environment
[encouraging voice] [applause]
[laughter]
now I have crossed 30.  Nowadays the atmosphere
is such that God may not be in the mood for this.
[laughter] I ca
n't.   I am
not even able to maintain fitness.  In the last two
years, I have gained 7-8 kg.
and I've Tried Everything But This
Is Not Going Anywhere.  They say change is
the only constant.  I'm like no this is.
[laughter]
This Mother for Refuge to Go.  Its concrete
foundation has been laid here.  [laughter]
I've tried everything.  Going to the gym.
Resistance Training Endurance 10,000
Steps HIIT Now we're on to Manifestation
[laughter]
[cheering]
[applause]
Oh Universe.  [laughter]
I'm ready for BMI.
So do everything come off late in order to get
fit.  I have resorted to sports now.
I have started playing badminton.
Hands down the worst decision of my life.
[laughs] Badminton is a very tough sport to
play.  I have seen that after the age of 30, one should
not play anything
[laughs] except cards.  Nothing and no
yes no don't play chess either.  The mind has become
garbage.  Absolutely.  While
playing badminton, I realized that there is a lag in my body
with respect to my intentions.
[laughter]
There [laughter] is a huge lag
between what I want to do and what I can do.
[laughs]
I'm standing in the court wearing shorts and holding a racket.   The
shuttle is seen falling near the net.
[laughs] There is also the intention to
pick it up.   The
body is saying run.
[Praise]
You will become Gopichand.
Which World Cup is taking you to play the next point
?  [laughter] It's
simple.  Day two of being on the
badminton court.  Day Two I pulled my hamstring.
But this matter of death has been
taken on the badminton court.  It is not taken while playing badminton.
[laughter]
Picking up the shuttle.  [laughter]
That's all that's left.  I am not able to come up.
[laughter] That's how I came out of court.   I went to
play badminton.  I myself have emerged as a shuttle [ __ ].
[cheering]
[applause]
[music]